Sunnyvale, CA (408) 320-8343 rodwoodman.com

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER Front-End Focused Full Stack Developer

Versatile and thorough Web applications developer who loves building dashboards that satisfy users. Embraces subjectivity in front-end data presentation with a grounding in full stack development experience. Balances systems thinking with attention-to-detail to solve whole-product challenges. Open collaborator driven to continually improve UX and simplify design complexity.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- <u>Code</u>: HTML, CSS, SASS, ExtJS, Angular, React, Highcharts, Python, Golang, MongoDB.
- <u>Tools</u>: REST APIs, VSC, Git, Bitbucket, vim, Sublime Text 2, Photoshop, Balsamiq, Omnigraffle.
- Methods: OOP, Continuous Integration, SPA, wikis, UX, user-centered design (UCD), wireframes.
- Soft skills: analytical, user-focused, communicative, collaborative, transparent, iterative.
- <u>Core values</u>: transparency, growth, perspective.

SAMPLE WEB APPS

- Boardgameinator: Board game comparisons; React, Bootstrap, BoardGameGeek.com API;
- ComparingStocks: Meaningful stock allocation data; React, Alpha Vantage API;
- TrailProfiler: Charts together GPX and JPG files; Vue, ChartistJS, Bootstrap;

EXPERIENCE

ARUBA NETWORKS, Santa Clara, CA

2016 - 2020

Senior Applications Engineer - Support Portal for Aruba Central Guest

- Jointly responsible on a team of 6 for a supportability interface to a Docker AWS NMS application.
- Added a RadSec capture UI, as well as Twilio and SendGrid API integration for troubleshooting.
- Documented and presented the ecosystem architecture over Confluence and Zoom.

Senior Applications Engineer - Config Sync tool for ClearPass

- Solely responsible for a new tool to audit and sync the configs of 100 ClearPass cluster at once.
- Designed and built the entire UI and internal APIs from informal product requirements.
- Released the major functionality of scheduling, reporting, filtering, exporting, backup and restore.

TRUEPATH WIRELESS, San Jose, CA

2015 - 2016

NMS Engineer

- Jointly responsible on a team of 2 for the Network Management System (NMS) product.
- Redesigned the UI for better network insights from the collected telemetry data.
- Sped up the pace of NMS improvements by releasing new code every 2-3 weeks.

CISCO SYSTEMS, San Jose, CA

2005 - 2014

Software Developer

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Master of Science in Computer Engineering - Santa Clara University, Santa Clara, CA
Bachelor of Science in Electronic Engineering - Cal Poly State University, San Luis Obispo, CA

MEAN Stack Blackbelt - Coding Dojo, San Jose, CA

Web Design Certificate - UCSC Extension Silicon Valley, Santa Clara, CA